I saw someone say the other day, I hate celebrating war.
And I think it's really important to understand celebrating balance.
Celebrating balance.
If we understand nature, we understand balance.
We understand that there are predators and prey.
And we understand that even though you don't necessarily want to see a soul gone,
that the balance of that, the circle of life, if you will,
is necessary for the harmony of the universe and the harmony of the ecosystem and of the planet.
We, as humans, have completely dislodged from harmony.
The reality is some people got to die for harmony to be restored.
The same way you got to pull weeds to protect your garden.
You can always look to nature to understand and to see, okay, am I bugging?
So when we hear people say things like, you know, an eye for eye makes the world blind.
First of all, that was said by Gandhi, who absolutely was not somebody that you should be quoting.
He was a bleeding heart racist and he was a PDF.
What the hell?
I mean, this is a what the hell moment.
And I want to know what kind of leaders are we following?
Over the coming years, he, Gandhi, began his controversial brahmacharya experiments.
Sleeping next to, oh my God, I can't even say it.
Sleeping next to naked woman, including his 16-year-old grand-knee's Abha,
to test the woe of his celibacy.
So let's stop with that.
Second, he was working in cahoots with the colonizers.
So him saying an eye for an eye makes the world blind supported his pacifist ideologies,
which by the way, Martin Luther King was following,
only to realize that day we were pacifists and then people was passing a fist into our faces.
So the pacifism nonsense, okay?
It's not even practical in nature.
Got him.
Gandhi was literally in there with Churchill talking about partition.
You know how many people died during partition and the creation of Pakistan?
You think it's a coincidence that they're doing this war during Ramadan?
Do you think that's a coincidence?
They thought these people in Iran were going to be too hungry to fight,
that their brains wouldn't be as sharp.
Because these people, they do not understand believing in something that is actually of life.
They don't understand that because what they believe in is destruction.
So they can't conceptualize that you would be during Ramadan physically hungry but mentally strong.
They can't conceptualize that.
Ramadan almost over though.
Ramadan almost over.
That's why they thought, oh, we're going to handle this in two weeks.
No.
We have to also always remember to give dua, to give thank you, to give praises to those whose lives are being sacrificed for the world to be better.
They're not the first.
They're not the last.
But they are the now.
And you should be lifting them up every day.
There's got to be a better way.
And we've got to.